<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eigen.sh</title>
    <link>https://eigen.sh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on eigen.sh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 15:23:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eigen.sh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manually Staking Cardano (ADA) to Maximize Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://eigen.sh/blockchain/manual-ada-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 15:23:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eigen.sh/blockchain/manual-ada-staking/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Would you like to make true 7% passive income off of your crypto? Sounds too good to be true right? Let&amp;rsquo;s talk.
In this guide we will be going over to how to manually stake Cardano to maximize rewards. The term &amp;ldquo;staking&amp;rdquo; may seem scary to crypto newbies, but this is really just a misnomer. We are following the Proof-of-Stake protocol, not staking our money in terms of gambling it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the 2020 Presidential Election using Support Vector Regression</title>
      <link>https://eigen.sh/projects/pres-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 13:46:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eigen.sh/projects/pres-ml/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I want to preface this by saying that this is a model that I created in college in one of my Machine Learning classes for a final project in 2016, but I figured it was cool enough to display publicly. Licenced by Tulane University Computer Science. Now it is 2021, and the 2020 Presidential Election has concluded. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how young Sam did on his ML model compared to what actually happened!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eigen.sh - an overview</title>
      <link>https://eigen.sh/posts/goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:46:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eigen.sh/posts/goals/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Before going any further, please take a look at the ABOUT section to learn a bit about me!
Welcome to eigen.sh - this is essentially my spot to play around with new technology and not feel bad about it by by using cloud hosted infrastructure. This site is hosted on GitHub pages and I directly push code and updates through there. Super easy if you want to build something fast and clean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://eigen.sh/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eigen.sh/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Sam Eigen. I graduated from Tulane University with a double major in Political Economy and Computer Science in May of 2020! Ever since then (COVID!) I&amp;rsquo;ve been stuck in my room going nuts! How nuts you may ask?
In the span of this past year, I have:
 Learned how to develop, deploy, and manage a full-stack iOS application w/ a super fun and collaborative AGILE team Became one of those annoying Vim people (sorry VSCode) Received all certifications in a major SIEM - shoutout Sumo Logic!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
